Hello.
I'm Yui Kobayashi from Sakura Sakamoto Shuji.
I'm Umei Ozora.
Well, where are you today?
I'm here in Sendai.
In this cherry blossom lover's release, I would like to go to Sendai's famous cherry blossom viewing spots earlier than the blooming of cherry blossoms.
Maybe go eat some delicious food?
I'm looking forward to it!
Let's Go to Sakura Tobi!
Let's go!
I think we might be a little underdressed.
Oh, really? Everyone in town is wearing downers and scarves.
We're a little, you know, underdressed.
Well, we're a little underdressed.
You smell good.
It smells so good!
Oh, it's Thai-yaki!
You like Thai food, don't you?
When?
I have an image of you as a Thai-yaki lover.
When did I eat Thai food?
I've never been.
Never?
I've never said I liked Thai food.
Well, we are on our way to appear on KHB East Japan Broadcasting's "Cheeky TV" right now!
Yes, the previous generation...live!
Ah, yes.
Last year.
Last year at a live performance.
We performed last year.
Is it a vacation at noon?
Vacation?
We're at KHB East Japan Broadcasting.
We're here.
I'll be appearing live on the air.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah, it's my first time.
Well, the live broadcast is over.
We're done.
That was fun.
What a surprise.
He's so cute.
This is Au and this is John.
There's so many of them.
Thank you very much.
So, are we going to have dinner after this?
I'm looking forward to it.
Here we are.
Lunch!
Beef bowl on rice!
Kyusuke!
Thick!
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
Hot!
Delicious!
Reminds me of the venue in Miyagi
Indeed.
I overslept a bit.
Mmm.
You can chew right through it, can't you?
Between the slits.
The more you chew, the more flavor comes out.
Applause!
Applause.
How was it?
The guy who shoots music videos.
The scene where I'm alone.
I was too far away.
If it's a scene with just one person...
With everyone else.
When we shot the last chorus.
When I was surrounded by everyone
I feel safe.
Aaah, everyone is here!
I felt it more strongly than ever.
It was the strongest feeling I've ever had.
Did you work hard?
Yeah.
So was renner.
Both of them.
I don't know.
I'm glad to see you've come out of your shell.
I'm glad.
Thank you for dinner.
It was delicious.
So...
I'm going to go now.
I have some free time.
I'm going to go to a place
I'm going to go somewhere.
I'll see you later.
That was rock-paper-scissors.
Oh, that's good.
Meets.
Meets.Meats.
Wow.
Ew.
That's too much.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's so close.
The latest pudding.
Cute pudding.
Cute.
We're here!
Here we are!
This is Nishi Park, Miyagi Prefecture's famous cherry blossom viewing spot.
They haven't bloomed yet.
But I can see some buds.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
They're doing their best.
I think they'll be in full bloom by April.
It's snowing.
Yes.
Big ego!
They're holding them up alternately.
Sakuragaoka
Daijingu
Cherry blossoms
That one!
Daijingu
This is Vivon
I wonder how far it will go.
It looks purple.
Chokichi Chokichi cute
Chokichi, Chokichi cute!
It's going to be a verdant cherry blossom!
I'm so happy! This is so cute!
This is awesome!
Oh, that's talent!
I'm so happy! Wow!
Great luck!
Great luck! Yay!
I'm going to bed now!
Good evening!
I'm going to go to the live broadcast of Mr. Rei Miyagi's program "Oban-desu".
Oban-desu!
Lantern's YouTube is over!
Thank you very much.
It's like a live broadcast.
Wow.
The last thing today is dinner.
Hamburgers.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to visit a customer.
I'm going to have a hamburger steak.
It's a very popular samburger steak.
Yes, it is.
It's very famous.
Some kind of Neapolitan.
They say it's the number one Neapolitan.
It's fun!
What do you mean by "worth"?
Is there a good performance in China?
Do you?
He says and speaks.
That's it.
I can paint it with one stroke.
I hope it lasts.
He says it's a big 8.
It's great if you can feel it.
Looks delicious.
It's the same.
I'm hungry and it looks delicious
I'll eat it
Looks delicious.
It's hot.
I'm so happy.
The noodles
Mochi Mochi!
I want to do this!
I definitely want to do this.
I definitely want to do this!
In this thimble
Third term students
Joined us.
How did you like it?
It's your first time, right?
When you're a senior.
It's the first time for me.
All the rankings and stuff.
I'm now a member of the third class.
Someone I look up to.
than my father.
I'm not writing.It doesn't say.
Why not?
Because it's on there.
I'm feeling like a third-year student.
It's funny.
You know, between the two.
At the cake shop.
There's a cake with hiragana.
It came in right away, so...
Like a junior.
I didn't have a lot of experience
I hadn't been in that position before.
It was just a moment.
As a junior.
I'd never do anything to you.
You had it, didn't you?
Make them laugh.
I'll make him laugh.
Ever.
These are the people who know everything.
Don't you think?
They're the ones who enjoy the current group.
I'm glad you said that.
They're the most enthusiastic.
I'm eating this right now.
It's fun.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
It's time to go home.
I've been asked to be on a local TV show.
I've had the pleasure of being on the show.
I had a great time eating delicious food.
I had a great time.
We went to some of the best places around.
Yes, I did.
All of you.
I hope you'll take a look at this
I hope you'll take a look at this before you go.
I'd be very happy.
Please take a picture!
Go to sakuratobi in Miyagi
That's it!
Bye bye!